like I said welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother tanzel and
God spake all these words saying I'm I
am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou sh have no other
gods con me thou shall not make it to
thee any Graven image or any likeness of
anything that is in heaven above or that
is in the earth Ben or that in a water
under the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children un the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that take of his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall thou leave in do
all thy Work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it thou
shall not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man's servant nor
thy M servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that's within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
rested the seven day wherefore the Lord
blessed the Sabbath day and hollowed it
honor thy father and thy mother that thy
days may be long upon the land which the
Lord thy God give thee th thou shall not
kill thou shall not commit adultery thou
shall not steal thou shall not bear
false witness against thy neighbor thou
shall not cover thy neighbor's house
thou not cover thy neighbor's wife nor
his man's servant nor his maid servant
nor his AR nor his ass nor anything that
is thy neighbors we read Exodus 21
through1 17 and may the Lord have a
blessing to the reading of his words in
Jesus name we pray
amen amen apologize for our tardiness we
had some technical difficulties but here
on question and answer you can ask us a
question and we'll answer it according
to the King James Bible and if we cannot
find the answer we will seek further
counsel to bring you an answer at a
later time the questions we will not
answer are the vague and long scripture
questions as well as questions of debate
we are here to spread the true Gospel of
Jesus so please be as direct as possible
with your questions so we can be as
direct as possible with our answers out
of the King James Bible no other Bibles
or books will be acknowledged on this
program also keep in mind that this is a
live stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce the family that's on
the panel this evening yeah brother Dre
good
evening got brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Jerome Grace and peace
Brother tanzel good evening sister
Deborah good evening and we have sister
Casey with us as well as the guest
caller I'm brother Cornell what is our
first question of the evening yes there
are several held over questions that
will be answered first before getting
into tonight's
Q&A uh thou
as do holy and evil spirits enter the
body or just linger according to the
Bible Luke 8 vers 30 through
33 and Matthew 12:
43-45 are given all right brother Jerome
deal with those holy as well as evil
spirits no none of the Angels uh enter
inside you take you over possess you
like you may see in a movie something
like that it doesn't happen that way
okay but they can influence you okay and
often times it's done by uh other people
that they're influencing you by what
they may be saying or what they might be
doing okay and so this is how they uh
they operate they influence people to do
do things and often times the wicked
ones try to influence you to go against
God okay so let's look at some examples
of that let's let's deal with judas's
scariot Okay so let's go to Luke
22 and we're going to read verse three
and it's going to sound
like you
know an evil angel is going inside him
but we going to show you what what's
really happening okay so go to that Luke
22 and read verse
three then enter Satan into Judah
certain name mcar being of the number of
the 12 yeah it says so then enter Satan
into Judas he not really going inside
Judas let me show you what's really
going on go to St John Chapter
13 and read verse
two St John
13 verse two an upper being ended the
devil having now put into the heart of
Judah es scarat Simon's Sons to betray
him so it said the supper being ended
the devil having now put into the
heart of Judas is scar to
betray Jesus so he influencing him to
betray Jesus and he did betray Jesus
okay so influence your mind right yeah
that's all I got on all right okay thank
you for that brother I hope that answer
their question as they try and keep that
mind clean moving on to our next
question moving on Miss Wade asked in
Matthew 20 verses
10-6 what does this mean the last first
the first last please explain all right
last is first and the first is last
brother Julius this is a question that
we get very often sisters and brothers
it is a parable about the kingdom of God
and those who worked in it those who
have been in for a long time and those
who at the last minute repent turn to
the true Living God and do that which is
right keep his Commandments and they
have a right to the tree of life that's
what this is really all about pick this
up tenzel at verse Matthew 20 read verse
one let's get the subject matter quickly
go ahead for the Kingdom of Heaven is
like unto a man that is in householder
which went out early in the morning to
hire labors into his Vineyard and that's
what we all are as professing Christians
we are all working in the vineyard of
the Lord continue quickly go ahead and
when he had agreed with the labors for a
penny a day he sent them into his
Vineyard now that now that's the pay
that's the pay for your labor working
this Penny represents your reward or
salvation in the kingdom of God go
ahead and he went out about the third
hour and saw other standing Idol in the
marketplace and he offered them the same
uh uh the same uh reward salvation skip
down to verse five continue again he
went out about the sixth and ninth hour
and did likewise all right at a
different time the more people at
different times same reward working in
the beyard Salvation verse
six and about the 11 hour he went out
and found other standing and said unto
them why stand ye here all the day
idle now uh skip down to verse eight and
go ahead so when evening was come the
Lord of The Vineyard said unto his
stewards call the laborers and give them
their higher beginning from the last
until the first beginning from the what
the last unto the first that means
whoever come in last gonna get the same
reward as the first that always been
doing the labor that started at an
earlier age at earlier time go ahead
brother
and when they came that were hired about
the 11th Hour they received Every Man a
penny they came in late and got
salvation just like the first ones
agreed to a penny a day for salvation
that's what this is all about now here's
the wrong attitude that we cannot have
verse
11 and when they had received it they
murmured against the good man of the
house uhhuh saying these last have rough
but one hour and thou H has made them
equal unto us and thou has made them
equal salvation is free to all sisters
and brothers whether you come late or
you come early the thief on the cross
came in at the last hour but he gonna
get salvation he recognized his
transgression and and confess and the
Lord say I'm telling you this day you
gonna be with me in Paradise when my
kingdom come finish it go ahead brother
which have borne the burden and heat of
the day go ahead and he answered one of
them and said friend I do thee no wrong
did is not thou agree with me for a
penny go ahead take that thine ears and
go thy way I will give unto the last
even as unto thee because why are you
complaining you are going to get
salvation yeah you started early and you
started you did right and you held on
but are Am I Wrong to give the people
that come in the people on the street
the pimp The Prostitute the whug
whatever the case might be am I wrong
when they turn to me and they seek
salvation
Am I Wrong to give them reward the same
reward salvation and I'm a merciful god
finish it bro isn't that lawful for me
to do what I will with my own yeah is
thy eye evil because I am good so the
last shall be first yes and the first
last yes for many he called but few
chosen so stop complaining we supposed
to be glad for The Sinner that because
the book say when one sinner returns uh
uh turns and repents you save a soul
from Hell the angels in heaven Rejoice
what are you complaining about you're
going to get salvation you working for
salvation wrong attitude we supposed to
be glad when whoever come in and
whenever they come in we are supposed to
be glad for them so the last going to
get salvation when they turn to God just
as well as the first cuz the Lord
created he can give salvation to whoever
he want to work out your own salvation
system Brothers with fear and trembling
that's all I got Cornel
all right thank you for that brother
hope that answer that question as we
move on to our next one next one
Marceline o Reed asks for you to explain
1 Corinthians 14 verse 34 the part which
also says the
law all right brother Dre what you say
about the
law let's go and read it and we will
deal with it 1 Corinthians 4
verse 34 Tel when you get it go
ahead let your woman keep Sil silence in
the churches for it is not permitted
unto them to speak but they are
commanded to be under obedience as also
sayth the law they are commanded to be
under obedience as also sayeth the law
let's go to Genesis the thir chapter
Genesis 3
Genesis the 3
chapter and we going to read verse 16
Genesis 3
and16 go ahead brother unto the woman he
said I will greatly multiply thy sorrow
and thy conception and sorrow thou shall
bring forth children and thy desire
shall be to thy husband and he shall
rule over thee so that's the law he
going to rule over thee but let's go to
Ephesians 5 and take a look at that
Ephesians 5 and we're going to start
that at verse 22 and read the
25 go ahead my brother when you get
why submit yourselves unto your own
husband as unto the
Lord for the husband is the head of the
wife even as Christ is the head of the
church he is the Survivor of the body
savior of the
body therefore as a church is subject
unto Christ so that the wives be to
their own husbands in
everything husband love your wives even
as Christ also loved the church and gave
himself for it that's right that's how a
husband should love his wife he's going
to rule his wife but rule her in
righteousness and that as also said the
law in Genesis 3
and16 that's all I
got all right
thank you for that brother hope that
answered that question as we move on
moving on Fitness Guru asks are we in
the New
Covenant yes caller are we in the New
Covenant yes we
are going to Jeremiah 31st chapter read
verses
31-34 Jeremiah 31
pick it up at
31 behold the days come sayth the Lord
that I will make a New Covenant with the
house of Israel and with the house of
Judah not according to the Covenant that
I made with their fathers in the day
that I took them by the hand to bring
them out of the land of Egypt which my
Covenant they break although I was a
husband unto them said the Lord but this
shall be the Covenant that I will make
with the house of Israel after those
days sayth the Lord I will put my law in
their inward parts and write it in their
hearts and will be their God and they
shall be my people and they shall teach
no more every man his neighbor and every
man his brother saying know the Lord but
they shall all know me for the least of
them unto the greatest of them say the
Lord I will forgive their iniquities and
I will remember their sin no
more okay now we're going to look at
this new covenant is he going to put his
loans in your inward part
and write them in your mind and he said
now once you do that nobody's going to
have to teach his neighbor no the the
neighbor that gets that that comes under
this Covenant and stud this word nobody
have to teach him but let me show you
when this New Covenant kicked in let's
go into Hebrews the 10th
chapter we're going to read one verse
one first then we're going to skip
down and read from 4 to six and when you
get through with six we going we going
to go from 9 10 but let's do one
first Hebrews 10 and one for the law
having a shadow of good things to come
and not the very image of the things and
can never with those sacrific for they
offer year by year continually make the
comers there unto
perfect now this this law it's talking
about the law animal sacrifice that mean
that the blood of these animal
couldn't make you become as they are
perfect in other words your sin couldn't
be forgiven and you couldn't be become
God now why is it skip down and read
verse uh
4 through uh uh uh
six for it is not possible that the
blood of bulls and of ghost should take
away sins wherefore when he cometh into
the world he said sacrifice and offering
thou wouldest not but a body has thou
prepared me and burnt offerings and
sacrifices for say thou H has no
pleasure now was that verse six yes sir
okay now the the blood of BU and ghost
could not remove sin therefore
De Jesus needed a body that could die
because Jesus was God before he was man
he was spirit being Spirit beings can't
die so he said sacrifice and offering
you didn't like because they couldn't
remove sin so a body you have prepared
me skip down to verse n let's go and
read n and
10 then said he lo I come to do thy will
oh God he take away the first that he
may establish the
second by the which will we are now you
take away the first what take away the
first Covenant that he may establish the
second you cannot have two covenants
running s simultaneously one replace the
other so he say taking away the first
that's the first Covenant that he might
establish the second Covenant go ahead
by
the by the which will we are Sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Jesus Christ once for
all now when that that that offering
when he was offered it was on the cross
when Jesus died on the cross that
terminated the old
Covenant wherein the blood of bulls and
goats was supposed to remove sin which
could not and established the New
Covenant whereas now you under the blood
of Jesus and Skip down the verse 14 and
go
ahead for by one offering he have
perfected forever them that I
sanctify well the Holy Ghost also is a
witness to us for after that he has said
before this is the Covenant that I will
make with them after those days sayeth
the Lord I will put my laws in their
hearts and in their minds will I write
them and their sins and iniquities will
I remember no
more so now when Jesus died on the cross
that terminated the old Covenant and
established the new that's why it was in
Jeremiah 31st chapter they said I put my
laws in their heart and write them in
their mind what verse was that uh
17 read Verse
18 now where remission of these is there
was no more offering for
sin so now when Jesus died on the cross
that was the beginning of the New
Covenant and the end of the old Covenant
so yes we
are in the New Covenant right now that's
all I have to say we started with death
of Jesus okay all right thank you for
that hope that aned your question as we
move on to our next question next
question Brit brat asks is it a sin to
do blood
transfusions isn't it considered like
ingesting it by it being injected into
your body Deuteronomy 12 verse6 and acts
15 verse 29 are given and she says we
must stay away from
blood all right so first of all um you
asked about you know is it sin to do
blood transfusions the answer is no a
lot of people lives are saved every day
by having to have blood transfusions but
then when you say the word ingesting
ingesting is like drinking you can in
ingest by drink drinking you can ingest
by eating and sometime even when you put
a patch on your arm they consider that a
form of ingesting as well but being
injected is not you actually putting it
through your mouth or trying to absorb
it for any other reason and saving your
life but let's go to that Deuteronomy 12
Deuteronomy 12
there and when you get there brother we
going to pick it up at that verse
16 Deuteronomy
12 and
16 and it's going to tell you here that
you are not to eat the blood which is
ingesting go ahead only ye shall not eat
the blood you shall pour it upon the
Earth as water all right so it's telling
you here that you're not supposed to eat
the blood you shall pour it out as water
now turn over to that acts 15 Act
15 and let's pick it up at that verse um
29 acts 15 and 29 it's going to be
talking about Meats a little bit more
and stuff of that nature go ahead that
ye abstain from Meats offer to Idol and
from blood and from things strangled and
from fornication from which if ye keep
yourselves ye shall do well Fair ye well
okay so it's telling us here about some
other thing meats and Idols but it tells
you also here and you shall stay away
from the blood talking about ingesting
it so let's go over to Leviticus the
thir chapter Leviticus
3 because there are some religions out
here that believe that you should not
get a blood transfusion and they watch
their loved ones perish because they
didn't want to get a blood transfusion
and that is nowhere in the Bible
Leviticus three and let's pick it up at
that verse 17 what does it say now this
is the ingesting part go ahead it shall
be a Perpetual statue for your
Generations throughout all your dwelling
that ye eat neither fat nor blood that
you eat neither fat nor blood you can
ingest the blood but you cannot eat it
by mouth so last place Deuteronomy
12 transfusion save lives every day all
around the world Deuteronomy 12 and
let's read that verse 15 and
16 not withstanding thou May kill and
eat flesh and all thy Gates whatsoever
thy Soul lusted after according to the
blessing of the Lord thy God which he ha
given Thee the unclean and the clean may
eat thereof as of the Rob and as so this
is talking about this is talking about
people here when it say the clean and
the unclean so we don't want nobody to
think that the dietary law has been
broken this is just talking about people
now read that verse 16 and that'll be it
only he shall not eat the blood you
shall pour it upon the Earth as water so
there we go yeah you shall not ingest
the blood you shall pour it out because
the Lord say that in the blood is life
so you're not supposed to ingest it but
you can inject it if it's transfusion to
save your life that's all I got let me
Let Me Wait in maybe somebody can find
it but the Lord was talking about about
like eating the fat and he said you
can't eat it but you can have use other
you can use it in other ways that's
Leviticus
7 Leviticus what Leviticus 7 and
26 2627 and then bag up and read
24 okay why don't somebody why don't you
do that
P all right we'll start at verse
26 moreover ye shall eat no man of blood
whether it be of Fire or of beast in any
of your dwelling to whatsoever so it be
that eateth any man of blood even thy
Soul shall be cut off from his people
24 and the fat of the Beast that die of
itself and the fat of that which is torn
with Beast may be used in any other use
but ye shall in no wise eat of
it see so now when you inject blood you
use it for another use but you're not
eating it what the Lord is saying is
when you cook some meat make sure the
blood is cooked out of it if you kill an
animal that you can't eat pull the blood
out and it's just like the fat you
cannot eat it but you can use it for
other use and other use is to if you
have to have a blood transfusion yes but
you just can't eat it just like that
said right there with that scripture
that's all I have to say and and brother
Cornell yes uh the definition of blood
transfusion is to transfer blood not eat
transfering blood from one person to
another I work at a hospital and I see
blood going from from uh one person to
another by way of a machine that's all
it means yeah but that ver four that
verse four that we read that that makes
it real clear yes sir that cleans read
that for one more time t
24 and the fat of the Beast that died of
itself and the fat of that which is torn
with Beast may be used in any other use
but ye shall in no wise eat of it same
thing with the blood
okay all right hope that answers your
question there as we move on to our next
moving on Rose Martin asks where in the
Bible can I find the land of minan and
as the place of safety after the
abomination of Destruction occupies the
holy
place yes
caller first thing is it's going it's
going to be the same Wilderness that we
was at let's go in Ezekiel 20th chapter
read verses 34-
36 Ezekiel 20th
[Music]
pick it up at verse 34 to
36 right and I will bring you
out from the people and will gather you
out of the countries wherein you are
scattered with a mighty hand and with
the stressed out arm and with Fury
poured out and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there would
I plead with you face to face like as I
pleaded with your fathers in the
wilderness of the land of Egypt so would
I plead with you sayeth the Lord God
now he's talking about bringing in the
last days he's said I'm going bring into
the Wilderness of the people what people
the same people that he brought into the
Wilderness when he brought out of Egypt
the same place Wilderness of the people
now let's go in there uh uh uh and let's
go and we going to find out because that
same Wilderness was before God uh Israel
end up talking to
God uh uh listening to God as he gave
them the ten commandments so let's find
out what that well that willing was
located at let's go into Exodus the 3
chapter and we're going to read uh uh
we're going to read start at verse one
Exodus 3 and
one Exodus 3 And1 now Moses kept the
flock of Jethro his father-in-law the
priest of Midian and he led the flock to
the backside of the desert and came to
the Mountain of God even to hor
now so this so Moses he went to back of
desert that was in the land of media cuz
remember he was keeping his father's law
flock so they went before the Mountain
of God and and and uh uh that's the same
Mountain that they went back to when he
took them out of Egypt so let's go into
Exodus the uh uh 19th Chapter read
verses one and two first
in the third month when the children of
Israel were gone forth out of the land
of Egypt the same day came they Into the
Wilderness of
Si for they were departed from refidim
and were come to the desert of Si and
had pitched in the wilderness and the
Israel came before the
mountain okay the same Mount it's called
HB and Si but it's the same Mount but
skip down to verse 10 read 10 and
11 and the Lord said unto Moses go unto
the people and sanctify them today and
tomorrow and let them wash their clothes
and be ready against the third day for
the third day the Lord will come down in
the sight of all the people upon Mount
Si so now this is in the wilderness one
last place Deuteronomy
4:5 because from now f is where lord
gave that speak and he and all the
people saw was fire and smoke cuz he
didn't want them to see no uh uh image
or anything because he didn't want you
to make no image or anything but read
verse
15 so take you therefore good heed unto
yourselves for ye saw no man of
similitude on the day that the Lord
spake unto you in whb out of the midst
of the
fire so now he called it horab again
that was in the land of Midian that was
the Wilderness and that's where we going
to go same Wilderness of the people
which is the Wilderness that our fathers
were in that's all I have to
say thank you for that hope that answers
your question and move on to our next
next one Malachi Blake asked will any
Israelite who might take the mark of the
beast make it to the
wilderness take the mark of the beast
will you make it to the Wilderness guess
call I don't know but I show you
something I do know go to Revelation the
14th chapter and read verse 9
through1 Revelation 14 verse
9 through
11 and the third Angel followed them
saying with a loud voice if any man
worshiped the Beast and His Image and re
receive his Mark in his forehead or in
his hand the saint shall drink of the
wine of the wrath of God which is poured
out without mixture into the cup of his
indignation he shall be tormented with
the fire and brimstone in the presence
of the Holy Angels and in the presence
of the
lamb and the smoke of their torment
ascended up forever and ever they have
no rest day or night worship the Beast
and His Image and whosoever receive the
mark of his
name so that's that's that fire that
fire indignation that smoke forever and
ever that's the Lake of
Fire so I don't know whether you get in
the wilderness if you survive a Great
Tribulation but I know if you take the
mark of the beast that's what you going
to get that's all I have to
say don't get the
mark okay
hope that aned your question as we move
on to our next one with the time check
yes the time is 810 me too for you Jones
asked in the Book of Jonah the people of
Nivea were they
gentil all right brother Julius what you
say Jerome Jerome my my apology brother
Jerome what you
got um no the people of Nineveh are not
Gentiles they hamites they actually come
out of the people of Assyria and they
referred to by their Biblical name in
Genesis so let's go take a look at it
Asher okay so let's go to uh
Genesis 10 and read verse 11 and we
going to do
Ezra and second Kings after that
Tel Genesis 10 and verse
11 out of that land went forth Asher and
buil Nineveh and the City of brobo and
Caleb okay yeah so the ninevites are are
are Syrian people okay uh now let's go
take a look at this Asher and tie it to
uh Syria that's just the Biblical name
for Assyria Asher okay so now let's go
to Ezra um chapter
4:2 book right after second
chronicles Ezra 4 right yeah verse
two and they came to
zerubabel and to the chief of the
fathers and said unto them let us bear
with you for ye seek your God as ye do
and we do sacrifice unto him since the
days of es Hardon king of Asher who
brought us up hither okay now this as a
as as a Harden king of Asher we gonna
see him again and he gonna be associated
with Assyria U through his through his
father okay so now let's go to Second
Kings chapter 19
and read verse 36 and
37 Second Kings 19 right yeah 2 Kings 19
verse 36 and
37 but the people held their peace and
answer him not a word for the king's
commandment was saying answer him not
NOS second KS 19 right yeah 2 Kings
19 verse 36 and
37 okay so sakar king of Assyria
departed and went and returned and dwelt
in
ninal and it came to pass as he was
worshiped in the house of nro his God
and Dr and Sh sherezar his son smoked
him with the sword and they escaped in
the hand of AR
Armenia and as Hardon his son rain and
instead yeah so yeah they that's who the
Asher is that's just the Biblical name
for
Assyria that's all I got him all right
thank you for that as we move on to our
next question next question leaping lamb
asks why do we flee Into the Wilderness
to be protected from Satan or
destruction or
Jesus why flee to the Wilderness brother
Julius
uh go to 9 Psalm
91 to plead the Great
Tribulation Psalm 91 and when you get it
t begin at verse one Psalm 91 not cuz
who can protect you from
Jesus Jesus is the one that's providing
the protection Psalm 91 and9 when you
get it 10 go ahead my brother 9 Psalm 91
And1 go ahead he that dwelleth in the
secret place of the most high shall
abide under the shadow of the almighty
Jesus is the almighty so you're under
his protection go ahead I will say of
the Lord he is my refuge and my Fortress
my God and in him will I trust skip down
uh well continue to read read quickly go
ahead surely he shall deliver thee from
the snares of the father and from the
nois and pestilence yes he shall cover
thee with his feathers and under his
wings shall thou Trust
and his and his truth shall be thy
shield and bucking man go
ahead thou shall not be afraid for the
terror by night nor for the arrow that
flyth by day nor for the pestilence that
walth in darkness nor for the
destruction that wasteth at noon day so
during the Great Tribulation there's
going to be destruction all around you
military hardware it is the place of
safety man skip down to verse 9 go ahead
why why do you have to flee to the
go ahead because thou Hast made the Lord
which is my refuge even the most high
thy in habitation go ahead one more
there shall no evil befall thee neither
shall any plague come not thy dwelling
and why is that read one more and we're
done for he shall give his angels charge
over thee to keep thee in all thy ways
so in the in that Wilderness you going
to be protected not one bullet not one
missile not one uh uh uh germ or
chemical warfare is going to come near
you it's going to be all around you but
nowhere near you why because you have
made the Lord by your faith and
obedience have made the Lord your
protector so you flee to the Wilderness
to protect you from the Great
Tribulation from receiving the mark of
the beast so and and so on and so forth
sisters and brothers that's why you it
is imperative that you understand and
get to the will when you see these
things the Lord say
flee that's all I got
Cornel all right yes sir that is the
real force
field all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next next
one Glenn Sirus ass is Moses wife
zoria the same woman that Miriam and
Aaron spake against in Exodus 12 verse1
Jay what you
say yeah let's go to Exodus 12 and verse
one and read
it read it you get it
Tel and the Lord spake unto Moses and
Aaron in the land of Egypt
saying so that's not that's not the
passage go to numbers 12 in verse
one numbers 12 and verse
one numbers 12 verse
and Miriam and Aaron spake against Moses
because of the Ethiopian woman whom he
had married for he had married an
Ethiopian woman yeah so you know you
look at this now let's go to Exodus the
2 chapter Exodus
2 and pick it up at verse
16 Exodus 2 and 16 go ahead when you get
it now the priest of Midian had seven
daughters
they came and Drew water and filled the
trough to the water their father's
flock and the Shepherds came and drove
them away but Moses stood up and helped
them and watered their
flock and when they came to rayu their
father he said how is it that ye are
come so soon today and they said and
Egyptian Deliver us out of the hand of
the Shepherds and also youw water enough
for us and water the flock notice they
called Moses an Egyptian here but Moses
was not an Egyptian right and then this
rul in another place his name is Jethro
go
ahead and he said unto his daughters and
where is he and why is he why is it that
ye have left the man but call him that
he may eat
bread and Moses was content to dwell
with the man and he gave Moses aor his
daughter mhm and she buried him a son
and he called his name gersin for he
said I have been a Stranger in a Strange
Land okay that's good so Moses wife
Zapora came from rul a
Jethro which was a
midianite which came through
Abraham's uh wife that he had coutura
the
Midwife that he dealt with
and like they say in Amos 9 and7 are you
not as the Ethiopians on to me what does
Ethiopia mean it means black a burnt
face that's all it
mean but Zapora
was was his wife we reading here right
you know you got in in Acts not acts 13
let's just go there and read that and
we'll stop it right there acts 13 and
one acts 13 And1 go ahead and read it
when you get
it now there were in the church that was
in Antioch certain prophets and teachers
as Barnabas Simeon that was called Niger
and Lucius of sirene and Manan which had
been brought up with Herod the tar and S
the Simeon was called called
Niger that just simply means
black that's all so when you dealing
with and and
Egypt the the name that it was called
before means black
land so we just talking about black
people right but Zapora was his
wife so is that the same uh woman that
Miriam and Aaron was talking about
absolutely
yes I have to take issue with that okay
yeah it's
Kor different women yeah so they said
was married Ethiopian woman that mean
she's a hamite and Zapora was a
shemite
yes okay I know you know that you just
forgot it okay yes sir all right yeah so
they were really talking about coutur
correct that's the no they they was
complaining against the Ethiopian you
know because told to marry outside the
nation right that's why the Lord told
them that mes was a proven servant to me
but it was the law of Israel not the
matter outside the nation it was not the
so Moses was compl they was complaining
because they married this Hite woman and
she was not an Israelite that's why they
talked against her that's when the Lord
turned Miriam
white yeah for a week okay
y all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one Epatha asked for you to explain
Isaiah 48 verse 16 the Lord and his
Spirit please explain who is the spirit
of the
Lord all right who is the spirit of the
Lord Brother
Jerome let's go read it Isaiah
48:16 Come Ye near unto me hear ye this
I have not spoken in secret from the
beginning from the time that it was
there am I and now the Lord God and and
his Spirit have sent
me yeah well that that spirit is the
literal word of God when we talking
about the word of the father okay so the
father sent Jesus they took sweet
counsel together and it was decided that
the one that became the
son he was sent by the father all right
so it's the literal word of God okay God
the Father yeah
and uh if you go to the 49th chapter
let's go to the 49th chapter you can you
can see a little example of it
there um pick it up at verse
one listen oh SS unto me and hearken ye
people from far the Lord have called me
from the womb from the bows of my mother
have he made mention of my name that's
the father and the one he talking about
in the womb that's Jesus go
ahead and have made my mouth like a
sharp Sword and the shadow of his hand
have he hid me and made me a polished
sha and in this quiver have he hid
me verse three and said unto me thou my
servant oh Israel in whom I will be
glorified as the father said unto Jesus
thou my servant oh Israel and Israel is
another one of Jesus's names he the one
that adopted the nation of Israel
that's all I
got I like to throw one thing
in yes sir the word that the the word
that Jesus spoke the same he got from
the father because he say speak only
what his father say yeah so so the
father and his Spirit sent him and I'm
going show you what that was the same
spirit that Jesus had go to St John 6th
chapter and read verse 6-3
it is the spirit that Quicken the flesh
propit is nothing the words that I speak
unto you they are spirit and they are
life so he's talking about his word
words that he speak unto you yeah so
father and his word that is what sent
Jesus his word saying you know and and
uh uh uh
those people think that uh that it's
talking about an individual just cause a
spirit job in the 21st chapter tell you
that talks about the spirit in his
nostrils that is the air that you
breathe through the father and so so so
is the word God in his word has sent him
because he had the same thing in Isaiah
61 we could go on and on but I just want
to let you know the spirit that he
talking about is the word of God
okay all
right okay we're going to move on to our
next question next question ly Mills as
are tattoos
sin
Julius First John 3 and4 let's read it
Tel First John 3 and 4 let's look at the
biblical definition of
sin whosoever committed sin sin
transgressive also the law for sin is
the transgression of the
law that's the Commandments the breaking
of the Lord's commandments let's go to
Leviticus the 19th
Chapter you know them in the Ten
Commandments thou shall not Thou shalt
not Thou shalt not Leviticus
19 and read verse 28
Brothers he shall make he shall not make
any cuting in your flesh for the dead
for the what for the dead for the dead
no cutting in your flesh for the dead go
ahead nor print any marks upon you I am
the Lord and we can read it nor pretty
the marks on you for the dead sisters
and
brothers so when you get those tattoos
you're getting they're cutting into your
skin and you're putting the marks on you
rest in peace uh Jerry rest in peace
Sally you know for the
dead that's what that means anybody want
to
add all right moving on to our next
question uh next question nor tap
says Jesus had the same body he went to
the Grave with are you saying that he
put on flesh and Bone just to deal with
men because he was raised a spirit with
all power do you Brothers think that it
is possible that a spirit body is flesh
and Bone like Jesus said he was after
his
resurrection he was a spirit being with
all power if Jesus put on flesh and Bone
after his
resurrection just to deal with men how
was he able to walk through walls and
pop up on the
people all right guess
call you
know I guess the same person brought the
same thing I've showed that that was
Jesus that talked with
Abraham and uh went on and and uh he
appeared to them as men but I want this
person to read
something since he made the thing do you
Brothers think and what's impossible and
what's I want to read something read
Luke 24 38 and
39 Luke
39 and he said unto them why are ye
troubled and why do thoughts arise in
your hearts
let
me oh who is this that's talking here
Jesus I want to make that clear now read
the next and finish it behold my hands
and my feet that it is I
myself handle me and see for a spirit
have not Flesh and Bones as ye see me
have who said that
Jesus I suggest brother you go when you
see Jesus you ask
him how it is that he can do something
impossible this is not coming out of our
mouth this is coming out of Jesus
mouth so what you doing you questioning
the power of
Jesus you asking the wrong person or the
wrong people next time you see him ask
him
and I see you brought the same thing up
again I'm going to give you the same
thing next time when you see Jesus ask
him what he said in Luke
2438 and
39 you asking the wrong person if he
said he call if he said he had Flesh and
Bones I'm not not W to question
him cuz if I remember he created us we
didn't create him you're asking the
wrong
people that's all I have to say all
right we leave it right there as we move
on to our next question next question
sers asked what country replaced Great
Britain in the European Union also was
Martin Luther King a false
prophet two-part question here guest
caller but the first thing is I don't
know who replaced uh Great Britain
yet but I know it got to be replaced
they out of it and as where as M Luther
King is is he a false prophet Martin
Luther King was a civil rights Advocate
and
leader that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
yes uh we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday March the 5th
2025 Gordon Scott says I know we have to
go through Jesus to get to heaven but
are there scriptures showing where the
Holy Father deals with us Like Jesus
Does in the Kingdom
all right well Gordon we like to first
of all say that um ain't no man going to
heaven or has ever been to Heaven except
for he that came down right no man no
woman no child except for he that have
came down everybody else has returned to
the dust of the ground if they have
passed away but let's go into uh John
the thir chapter John
three and let's pick it up at verse 13
John 3 and read that verse
13 go ahead and no man have ascended up
to heaven but he that came down from
heaven even the son of man which is in
heaven so no man have ascended up to
heaven but he that came down from heaven
so when you ask about um do you have to
go through Jesus to get to heaven you're
not going there nobody is and we
understand that that's a popularity
teaching but it is incorrect so let's go
over to John 8 John
8 get to John
8 let's pick it up at that verse 8 John
8 and 8 and then we're going to do some
skipping here go ahead John 8 and 12 I'm
sorry John 8 And1 12 go ahead then spake
Jesus again unto them saint
I am the light of the world he that
followeth me shall not walk in darkness
but shall have the light of life and you
follow Jesus by walking in his word down
here on this Earth skip down to verse 21
and let's see what else Jesus said go
ahead then said Jesus again unto them I
go my way and ye shall seek me and shall
die in your sins whether I go he cannot
come and he say whether I go ye cannot
come this is our Jesus mouth so we know
that once he died for the sins of the
world he was going back to heav to sit
on the right side of the father and he
told us right here that hey you cannot
come keep
reading then said the Jews will he kill
himself because he said whether I go ye
cannot come
uhhuh and he said unto them ye are from
beneath I am from above ye are of this
world I am not of this world so we are
beneath we came out the dust to the
ground Jesus came down from heaven
himself to put on this filthy flesh to
die for the sins of the whole world so
hey like he said ye are from beneath I
am from above ye are of this world I am
not of this world so no no man woman or
child is ever been there or is going
there and that's all I got on that first
part part of that question and sister
Deborah if you could repeat that second
part brother Julius will share some
light on that yes uh but are there
scriptures showing where the Holy Father
deals with us Like Jesus Does in the
Kingdom uh let's go to St John the 5th
chapter
10 the Jesus is the spokesman for the
father he is the word of God say John
5 and read verse
37 and the father himself which have
sent me have borne witness of me he have
neither heard his voice at any time nor
seen his shape now let's go on over to
St John the 12th
chapter St John 12 and 49
50 I have not spoken of myself but the
Father which sent me he gave me a
commandment what I should say and what I
should speak and I know that his
commandment is life
Everlasting whatsoever I speak therefore
even as the father said unto me so I
speak so Jesus is a spokesman for the
father he has always dealt with us
through his son that's why the books
they took weet counsel together came up
with with this Plan of Salvation so that
we can obey it bias and all the way up
until uh Jesus Kingdom and and then the
father then Jesus turns all power back
over to the father let's go to the last
place let's go to Revelation the 20th
chapter you know I mean this I mean we
can't go no further than what the book
tells us right and look at Revelation 21
1 go
ahead Revelation 21 And1 uhhuh and I saw
a new Heaven and a new Earth the first
Heaven and the first Earth were passed
away and there was no more sea uhhuh and
I John saw the holy city New Jerusalem
coming down from God out of Heaven
prepared as a bride adorned for her
husband uhuh and I heard a great voice
out of Heaven saying behold the
Tabernacles of God is with men
and he will dwell with them and they
shall be his people and God himself
shall be with them and be their God go
ahead brother and God shall wipe away
all tears from their eyes and there
shall be no more death neither sorrow
nor crying neither shall there be any
more pain for the former things are
passed away give me one more and he that
sat upon the throne said behold I make
all things new and he said unto me write
for these words are true and faithful
and then he tell you at verse six I'm
Alpha and Omega the beginning of the end
so hey he the father has always dealt
with us through his son and that's all I
got yes sir brother Julius New Jerusalem
is coming down no one's going
up it's coming
down all right thank you for that as we
move on to our next question uh next one
is from D law D law
says Hebrews 8 verse 8 why is the
Covenant renewed only with the nation of
Israel who broke the Covenant in Mount
Si is the nation of Judah under the same
laws and then he gives uh Hebrews 31
Jeremiah 31 and Leviticus 26 without any
versus all right so D um we're not going
to spend time on this question because
it has broken the rules for our plat
platform and first of all you said
Hebrews 31 there is no Hebrews 31 then
you mentioned Jeremiah 31 the whole
chapter Leviticus 26 the whole chapter
we don't have time to deal with that on
one question because we wouldn't have
time for the rest of our viewers and the
questions that are presented to us so we
asking that please when you send us a
question just submit two scriptures with
a couple of verses two scripture maximum
and then we'll try and answer your
questions from there but this question
here too lengthy too long please
resubmit let's move on to our next
question sister yes moving on Nicholas
asks you to explain Matthew 10 verse 28
I thought the body was the soul
okay let's share some light on what they
thought here in that Matthew 10 let's go
there 10l verse 28 then let's open it up
to the ptim Matthew 10 and verse
28 and fear not them which kill the body
but are not able to kill the soul but
rather fear him which is able to destroy
both soul and Body in
Hell let me deal with that
all
right because this is this is either see
uh uh the Lord tell you out of the mouth
of two or more witnesses of the fact
established is that correct that's right
that is correct the first thing is let's
go to the beginning and find out what
man
is let's go
into Genesis 2 and read verse 7
and the Lord God formed man of the Dust
of the ground and breathed into his
nostril the breath of light and Man
became a living
soul and Man became a living Soul that's
one time that's once ain't that correct
yep First Corinthians the 15th
chapter I think it's around verse
45 and read it
and so it is written the first man Adam
was made a living Soul the last Adam was
made a quickening spirit and so it was
written the first man Adam was made a
living
Soul coincide with genes with Moses
didn't it yep now we got uh
Matthew was there when Jesus Jus made
this spe but also Luke was there the
same was there also so now let's see
what Luke
said that Jesus said let's go into Luke
the 12th
chapter and read verse 4 and
5 and I say unto you my friends be not
afraid of them that kill the body and
after that have no more that they can do
but I will for warn you whom ye shall
fear fear Him which after he ha killed
have power to cast into hell yeah I say
unto you hear
him now they heard the same speech but
he didn't said nothing about Soul there
didn't he
no because the body is the
soul right now Matthews uh uh uh
Matthews was do like uh uh uh
uh Lord said about Israel he said he
Israel and give give here oh Jacob don't
he say that y now let's look let's look
at Matthews and read that
again one more
time pay
attention Matthew 10 and
28 and fear not them which kill the body
but are able to kill the soul but rather
fear
him but rather fear him which is able to
destroy both Body Soul and Body in Hell
wait a minute why the soul and Body in
hell you mean he going to snatch the
soul outside the body and he's still
going to destroy them in the same
hell one and the
same because all he's saying is just
what Luke said him that after he killed
can cast you into the Lake of Fire right
otherwise why would Jesus uh uh uh uh
say you can't kill the soul but still he
going to put them both in the hell ain't
that's what the book
say the ne one like I said God breathed
into his M and Man became a living Soul
Breath of Life and Man became a living
soul in 1 Corinthians 15:45 the first
man Adam was made a living
so and these guys ain't saying nothing
different all Peter is saying in
Matthews here is saying the body which
is the
soul he can cast into hell that's why I
said
both but the book said out of the mouth
of two or more witnesses is the fact
established
mes through
Moses Luke
and
Paul said the body is the soul that's
all I have to say all right thank you
for that hope that answers your question
as we move on to our next one next one
time out Houston ask is leviathan in
Isaiah 27
verse1 and Psalm 74
ver14 a real creature or just a symbol
and is it connected to the seven headed
dragon in
Revelation so Isaiah 27 verse1 and Psalm
verse4 is leviathan a real creature or
just a
symbol let's go to Isaiah 27 first pick
it up at verse one and we talk about the
piercing serpent even Leviathan and then
let's open it up to the panel after we
read that Psalm 74 and4 unless somebody
want to expound on that verse one go
ahead brother and that day the Lord with
his sore and great and strong sword
shall punish Leviathan The Piercing
serpent even Leviathan in that crooked
Serpent and he shall slay the dragon
that is in the
sea open to the
padle guess caller you got something for
that I don't know
is May somebody else
know um depends upon on the context
which is written another scripture say
he got
scales well let's um let's go into you
got let's go into our Psalm
74 and let's see it
there what we say about that one Psalm
74 and pick it up at that verse 14 when
you get
there thou breakast the heads of thethan
in pieces and gavest him to be meat to
the people inhabiting the
Wilderness all right open to the panel
on
that I like whatever it is it can be
killed I don't
know and maybe
eaten
right yep gave us him to be meat so
that's all um it's all we can really lay
out on that one a no scripture that
really explain what this
is uh who it might represent so being if
we can't read nothing directly we can't
answer that question so uh the other
part then uh is it and is it connected
to the seven headed dragon in
Revelation seven headed drag what seven
headed
dragon with the seven heads and 10 horns
no connection no
connection that's that's the European
that's that's the European Union and all
and the Gentile
Dynasty not a dragon those are that is
the that is the uh uh
uh Gentile nation that ran this world
from Nebuchadnezzar down to the European
Union
yeah when you saw a stood before the
woman with seven heads and T horns all
that mean is that these Gentile Nations
represent you know is ruled by Satan
that's why Paul said Gentiles sacrifice
the
Devils is not a dragon as a definition
of the Gentile Dynasty from
Nebuchadnezzar down to the European
Union
that they are putting back together this
very day that we
speak that represent me yep all right
hope that answered your question there
next one next one Malicia Cur ass will
Every Nation be gathered in the
wilderness when the children of Israel
go will Every Nation be gathered in the
go open to the
p
no there going to be some mixed
multitude but it's not going to be every
nation just like it was out of uh
uh Egypt who came out of Egypt mixed
multitude now let's go into uh Ezekiel
the 20th chapter and look at it
Ezekiel
20 we start read at
verse maybe
[Music]
32 okay read
it and that which cometh into your mind
shall not be at all that ye say we will
be as the Heen as the families of the
country to serve wood and stone but as I
live said this is what he telling Israel
he said that's not not that's not going
to be in your
mind that's not going to happen where
you said we're going to be like the
Heathen which is the
Nations Pagan God so he talking about
Israel go ahead last I live say the Lord
God surely with a mighty hand and with a
stressed out arm and with Fury poured
out I rule over you and I will bring you
out from the people and will gather you
out of the country wherein you are
scattered with a mighty hand and with a
stretched out arm and with Fury poured
out and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to
face like as I pleaded with your fathers
in the wilderness of the land of Egypt
so would I plead with you said the Lord
God so who who Who's were the fathers
that come out of Egypt
Israel Israel not all the nations go
ahead and I will call you to pass under
the rod and I will bring you into the
bond of the Covenant and I will Purge
out from among you the rebel and them
that transgress against me and I will
bring them forth out of the country
where they sourn and they shall not
enter into the land of Israel and ye
shall know that I am the Lord
show you he's talking about Israel read
the next
verse as for you oh House of Israel thus
sayith the Lord
God so go ye serve ye everyone his idols
and Hereafter also if you would UNH
harken unto me but pollute ye my holy
name no more with your gifts and with
your
Idols so the Holy Name That e polluting
is the name of Israel so no All Nations
not going to go to the Wilderness you
got other scripture
uh maybe somebody can run it down right
quick where he said they shall all turn
to their own people and they shall all
flee to their own
countries that's when this when the
Great Tribulation
start everybody run that down right
quick all right in search mode
still search Jeremiah 50 Jeremiah 50
and6 okay Jeremiah now Jeremiah 40 wait
a
minute Isaiah 13th
chapter yeah verse 14 Isaiah 13 and
begin at verse 14 yeah Isaiah 13 and 14
yeah 13 and 14 yeah that's
it and it shall be at the Chase Road and
as a sheep that no man taketh up they
shall every man turn to his own people
and flee everyone to his own
land that's when that's when the Lord
bring the drama and and and and the
tribulation to all the all the
people that uh uh all the people that
are are French they going to turn into
to the French all the Germans to the
Germans all the Italians to the
Italians all the hamites to the hamite
they all going to turn to their own
people and they all going to flee to
their own land and the Lord is going to
take Israel Into the Wilderness and then
into his own land that's all I have to
say yeah it going be under their own
Vine and under their own fig
tree all right
hope that ansed your question as we go
to our next one with the time check yes
the time is
8:55 Renee Israel asked in Revelations
11 verse2 come up hither will those be
the same words Jesus will say to the
ones in John 5 verse 28 and 1
Thessalonians
4: 16-1 17
right so you went over our limit sister
but we going to be nice with this
Revelation 11 and 12 because you got
three here but let's go to Revelations
11 and
12 and read it when you get there
brother and we going open it up to the
panel as we move through as we coming
down to a
crow and they have heard a great voice
from Heaven saying unto them come up
hither
and they ascended up to heaven in a
cloud and their enemies beheld
them well well well it's not going to be
but one time first Thessalonians said
read that start at verse uh uh 4 and
verse
13 but I would not have you to be
ignorant Brethren concerning them which
are asleep that ye sorrow not even as
others which have no hope but if we
believe that Jesus died and rose again
even so them also will sleep in Jesus
will God bring with
him but this will
say go ahead guess
caller I said keep
reading for this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord that we which are alive
and remain until the coming of the Lord
shall not them which are asleep for the
Lord himself shall descend from heaven
with a shout with the voice of the
Archangel and with the Trump of God and
the dead in Christ shall rise
first then we which are alive and
remains shall be caught up together with
them in the clouds to meet the Lord in
the air and so shall we ever be with the
Lord so that's not going to happen one
time
trumpet
blow or give a
shout and you go back on your own and
read when Joshua took down uh uh uh
Jericho Jericho blew the trumpet and
then what they did what the people
do dout it gave a shout the fall walls
fell
down and so this so that shout we know
what it is it is come up here go
Revelation the 20th chapter that the
people there uh in the first
resurrection so if these two witnesses
Rose before the rest of the people then
that wouldn't be the first resurrection
wouldn't it
nope so the shout is come up
here one and the
same and and then John 5 and 28 they
mentioned that one too right de what's
it say uh yes uh John 5 verse 28 correct
let's read that one and that will be our
last script of the
evening John
5 marel not
at go ahead Marvel not at this for the
hour is coming in the which all that are
in the grave shall hear his
voice same time same
thing same thing
y so and th
Thessalonians uh 4 where it says that
those that are alive and remain shall be
caught up together with them in the
clouds to be with the Lord everybody on
this panel and everybody got wisdom and
knowledge is looking forward to that
beautiful
day all right sister de time chck the
time is
a59 all right well we're going to close
it out right there we have ran out of
time and we' like to thank everybody
from all around the
world sorry guest caller go
ahead we got uh uh we got one more I
want to answer this same brother that
sent this same thing on the so-call
night was this Nish what it is somebody
said Nish
tape no is
take
okay uh you're talking about the comment
he made
yeah uh I wasn't uh
disputing that
question if Jesus put on Flesh and Bones
after his talking about okay guess call
you telling about question two in
tonight's de but read question two in
tonight
okay uh it was added already to number
uh the other one but I will read it
again if Jesus put on flesh and Bone
after his resurrection just to deal with
men how was he able to walk through
walls and pop up on
people go to Luke 24th chapter again
this time read start at verse 36
from 36 to39 again read
it and as they thus spake Jesus himself
stood in the midst of them and said unto
them peace be unto you but they were
terrified and frightened and suppose
that they had seen a spirit and he said
unto them why are you troubled and why
do thoughts arise in your hearts behold
my hands and my feet that it is I myself
and handle me and see for a spirit have
not Flesh and Bones as you see me
have now look at that that they was
there meeting together he popped up in
the middle of
them so
now and he said handle me some going to
said to this person again you need to
consult the Lord because uh he said said
it happened his Apostles wrote it it's
obvious you don't think that the
apostles knew the truth and you don't
think that Jesus have the power to do
whatever he want to
do so you uh write that down on a note
put it in your pocket and when you see
the Lord
asking that's all I have to say all
right
Deborah yeah did you do you see him in
the chat I see him in the chat and he's
responding right yes um right what he
stated was I wasn't disputing the fact
that Jesus was Flesh and Bones because
he said he was I was asking why did you
say that he made himself human so that
his Apostles would know him
I gave an
example just like he came upon
Abraham you understand I in the form
of and then Abraham said you know let me
uh uh uh uh trouble you to make you give
you something to eat so they kill the
FED calf break bread and fed ain't
that's what the book said yeah yeah they
come they look like man Lord and his two
angels and they ate like
men I quoted the scripture I didn't say
that we read that didn't we yeah yeah
let you know that the Lord had the power
to be whatever he want to be and to
appear like whatever he want to
appear and his power is not the question
so it's not you say it it's what we
read that's correct and even even when
he he he came in Flesh and Blood a body
was prepared for him it's all that
simple but the whole thing I'm saying is
he showed up like Abraham and you know
and ain't the only time he showed up no
but the is like the Apostle Paul said be
a be uh uh careful treat how you treat
trangers because you might be
entertaining an angel and unaware that
mean that he look like a man don't he
yep
so the Lord can do whatever you want he
look like whatever you want and whatever
he
say if you have an issue with it ask
him say good night all right good night
to you and we're going to say good night
to all of our family that have joined us
this evening for question and answer we
want to thank you all and we want to say
that if you submitted a question we
never chance to get to it don't resubmit
it sister Deborah going take it put it
in rotation we'll deal with that
question next Wednesday but we want to
say until we all come together again be
safe out there be blessed stay prayed up
and may the Lord have mercy on us all as
brother tanzel closes us
out all right Our Father which are in
heaven Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom
come thy will be be done in earth as it
is in heaven give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debtors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name